[
    {
        "question": "1 x 1 = ?",
        "answer": "1",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 2 = ?",
        "answer": "2",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 3 = ?",
        "answer": "3",
        "times_wrong": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 4 = ?",
        "answer": "4",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 5 = ?",
        "answer": "5",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 6 = ?",
        "answer": "6",
        "times_wrong": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 7 = ?",
        "answer": "7",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 8 = ?",
        "answer": "8",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 9 = ?",
        "answer": "9",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 10 = ?",
        "answer": "10",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 1 = ?",
        "answer": "2",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 2 = ?",
        "answer": "4",
        "times_wrong": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 3 = ?",
        "answer": "6",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 4 = ?",
        "answer": "8",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 5 = ?",
        "answer": "10",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 6 = ?",
        "answer": "12",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 7 = ?",
        "answer": "14",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 8 = ?",
        "answer": "16",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 9 = ?",
        "answer": "18",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 10 = ?",
        "answer": "20",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 1 = ?",
        "answer": "3",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 2 = ?",
        "answer": "6",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 3 = ?",
        "answer": "9",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 4 = ?",
        "answer": "12",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 5 = ?",
        "answer": "15",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 6 = ?",
        "answer": "18",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 7 = ?",
        "answer": "21",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 8 = ?",
        "answer": "24",
        "times_wrong": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 9 = ?",
        "answer": "27",
        "times_wrong": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 10 = ?",
        "answer": "30",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 1 = ?",
        "answer": "4",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 2 = ?",
        "answer": "8",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 3 = ?",
        "answer": "12",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 4 = ?",
        "answer": "16",
        "times_wrong": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 5 = ?",
        "answer": "20",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 6 = ?",
        "answer": "24",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 7 = ?",
        "answer": "28",
        "times_wrong": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 8 = ?",
        "answer": "32",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 9 = ?",
        "answer": "36",
        "times_wrong": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 10 = ?",
        "answer": "40",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 1 = ?",
        "answer": "5",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 2 = ?",
        "answer": "10",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 3 = ?",
        "answer": "15",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 4 = ?",
        "answer": "20",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 5 = ?",
        "answer": "25",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 6 = ?",
        "answer": "30",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 7 = ?",
        "answer": "35",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 8 = ?",
        "answer": "40",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 9 = ?",
        "answer": "45",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 10 = ?",
        "answer": "50",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "6 x 1 = ?",
        "answer": "6",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "6 x 2 = ?",
        "answer": "12",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "6 x 3 = ?",
        "answer": "18",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "6 x 4 = ?",
        "answer": "24",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "6 x 5 = ?",
        "answer": "30",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "6 x 6 = ?",
        "answer": "36",
        "times_wrong": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "6 x 7 = ?",
        "answer": "42",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "6 x 8 = ?",
        "answer": "48",
        "times_wrong": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "6 x 9 = ?",
        "answer": "54",
        "times_wrong": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "6 x 10 = ?",
        "answer": "60",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 1 = ?",
        "answer": "7",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 2 = ?",
        "answer": "14",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 3 = ?",
        "answer": "21",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 4 = ?",
        "answer": "28",
        "times_wrong": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 5 = ?",
        "answer": "35",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 6 = ?",
        "answer": "42",
        "times_wrong": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 7 = ?",
        "answer": "49",
        "times_wrong": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 8 = ?",
        "answer": "56",
        "times_wrong": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 9 = ?",
        "answer": "63",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 10 = ?",
        "answer": "70",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 1 = ?",
        "answer": "8",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 2 = ?",
        "answer": "16",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 3 = ?",
        "answer": "24",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 4 = ?",
        "answer": "32",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 5 = ?",
        "answer": "40",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 6 = ?",
        "answer": "48",
        "times_wrong": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 7 = ?",
        "answer": "56",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 8 = ?",
        "answer": "64",
        "times_wrong": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 9 = ?",
        "answer": "72",
        "times_wrong": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 10 = ?",
        "answer": "80",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 1 = ?",
        "answer": "9",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 2 = ?",
        "answer": "18",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 3 = ?",
        "answer": "27",
        "times_wrong": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 4 = ?",
        "answer": "36",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 5 = ?",
        "answer": "45",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 6 = ?",
        "answer": "54",
        "times_wrong": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 7 = ?",
        "answer": "63",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 8 = ?",
        "answer": "72",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 9 = ?",
        "answer": "81",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 10 = ?",
        "answer": "90",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 1 = ?",
        "answer": "10",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 2 = ?",
        "answer": "20",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 3 = ?",
        "answer": "30",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 4 = ?",
        "answer": "40",
        "times_wrong": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 5 = ?",
        "answer": "50",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 6 = ?",
        "answer": "60",
        "times_wrong": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 7 = ?",
        "answer": "70",
        "times_wrong": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 8 = ?",
        "answer": "80",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 9 = ?",
        "answer": "90",
        "times_wrong": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 10 = ?",
        "answer": "100",
        "times_wrong": 1
    }
]
